Thank you for watching!
The rehearsal is about to start
I'm going to practice changing my
clothes before the rehearsal
It's an important opening
I have to change my clothes during the
video, so I'm going to go
I'm going to the rehearsal
I'm so happy!
The girls are having fun with the
water.
Wow!
It's big!
There are three characters on the
water.
What's yours, Chie?
Kuromi?
If you say purple, it's Kuromi.
I'm Ko-chan.
The girls are having fun with the
water.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6.
Dance on!
We are the Jyokai Girls.
We will show you our dance.
Jyokai Girls
This is our first time ever to practice
in a team.
I changed my clothes.
I'm going to go.
Thank you for watching!
I'll take you to a different tomorrow
Don't hesitate
Even if we're apart
I won't lose my treasure
Because you gave it to me
Don't be afraid
To a wide world
I'll pick up the wings
Until the day we can meet everybody,
we must join hands.
Because we are kids with no idea.
Thanks for coming here today.
We appreciate it.
We're sorry.
Thank you for coming.
Don't mention it.
Good luck!
Yeah, alright.
I'm ready.
We have about 5 minutes left until the
show starts.
How many minutes before the show
starts?
10 minutes.
10 minutes before the show starts.
Aki, what's your makeup today?
I asked Hiori to do my makeup.
I see.
She likes her hair to be curled, and I
like my hair to be straight.
I'm a high school girl.
I see.
Please order our new album.
You can find it on Twitter.
Please try it.
Let's do our best!
All my love is for you
I was told I'm still doing it
This smell
I'm not a dog
I'll do my best
Mom, Mom
I'm going
It's my first time being on a filming
set too.
I write all the lines.
Where'd her lines added together?
Oh was something written?
I'm squeeking as I'm getting ready for
this.
Ready...
I'm getting a bit jealous, Karabi.
A bit!
I don't think it's good.
I might steal Piyo's.
Don't steal me.
Don't fight for me.
Oh my god.
Let's talk.
Thank you for coming to the spring 33
Hall Rock On Tour 2022 of Super Exciting
Advertising Department.
I'm Hito-chan, a super excited Red, and
I'm Hitoka Sakai.
I'm Haruka Koizumi, a super excited
Pink.
Thank you for coming to the spring 33
Hall Rock On Tour 2022.
We would like to take this opportunity
to thank you for your support.
We will be performing soon.
Yes!
How are you feeling today, Koizumi-san?
I'm feeling great!
What did you eat today?
What did I eat today?
I ate Chinese food.
I ate cake.
I ate Obayaki.
You ate Obayaki.
It was delicious.
Obayaki was delicious.
I will do my best with energy.
I will do my best.
Hiyori was eating a pan yame.
Then wait for me.
Bye bye.
Let's do it.
Let's start.
Okay, let's start.
Kanami!
Julia!
Toka!
Haruka!
Aki!
Hiyori!
Super-exciting advertisement!
Let's go!
It's not good.
The cannonball is hitting me.
Why?
It's good.
Please.
I'm really looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it.
Bye-bye.
Please subscribe to this channel.
my heart almost stopped
No no!
30 seconds left.
3, 2, 1, start!
We'll be there soon.
The first time we did a hall live was
like a Christmas event.
We started with the situation that it
was difficult to call so many fans.
But today is the first day of the
event, and it's a hall tour.
I'm so happy to come here and feel the
size of Nakano Sun Plaza again.
I'm so happy that fans can come here as
a tour.
Thank you so much for meeting and
finding me.
We will continue to hold a large live
performance called Makuhari Messe, and
we will continue to accelerate our
activities.
I hope you will continue to support us.
Thank you so much for today.
I'm so happy to be back at Nakano Sun
Plaza for the hall tour.
This place is filled with memories for
me.
I was working hard to make Nakano Sun
Plaza a good place for a year.
I'm so happy to be back here for the
hall tour.
I'm sure some of you have started a new
life.
I joined Tokizen when I was in the
third grade of junior high school.
I've been growing up with the staff and
the audience since then.
I'm sure this hall tour will be a great
opportunity for me to grow up with the
staff.
I hope you will cheer up when you are
having a hard time.
Let's make great memories together.
Thank you so much for today.
Thank you so much for coming today.
I can see that you are waving your
penlights during the live.
Thank you so much.
As Kanamin and Julia said,
I'm so happy that we can have a live
here
as one of the tour's venues,
not as one of the big Christmas live.
I'm so happy that more people love us.
Will you make more memories with us?
Thank you very much.
We love the memories we make with
everyone.
Let's continue to have a wonderful time
together.
Thank you very much.
When I sang the best melody of my life,
everyone said that the moment when we
first performed at Nakano Sunplaza was
very memorable.
I was very grateful that I could come
back as a tour.
I remembered various memories and I was
glad I didn't have to give up.
I'm sure everyone was glad that they
didn't give up with the same feeling.
I was very happy about that.
As Haru-chan said, we received a lot of
love from many people and staff.
I think that we are loved and supported
a lot.
April is the season of meeting.
When everyone is sitting like this, I
can see the faces of more people
clearly.
I was looking at it while thinking that
it was a great number of people.
I hope that everyone will be able to be
like us,
and I want to be a person who can
support us.
Let's make a lot of memories from now
on.
Thank you very much.
I always see HIURI on the stage with
the members,
and I can see that she is enjoying the
members' expressions from the bottom of
her heart.
I feel like we're having a fun live
together today,
and I'm very excited and enjoying this
space with everyone.
This tour has a screen, so it's easier
for everyone to see each other's
expressions.
It's easier to convey the expressions
we're enjoying to everyone.
Everyone is really enjoying it from the
bottom of their hearts.
I hope that TOKISEN will convey the
wonderful lyrics of the song
and the message that we're thinking
about from the bottom of our hearts.
I thought that TOKISEN's songs were
really good through this tour.
I hope you'll listen to the songs we
heard today on your way home
and feel that we're singing from the
bottom of our hearts.
I'll do my best to make a lot of
memories with you,
and I'll do my best to create a lot of
opportunities to meet you.
I'd be happy if you could support us.
We'll do our best to make a lot of
special days,
so please continue to support us.
Thank you so much for today.
Thank you so much for the Tokyo
concert.
Thank you for your hard work.
It was fun.
Thank you.
Thank you for your hard work.
It's over.
I was so nervous.
Life is so tough.
Thank you for your hard work.
This tour is a theme.
There are many tours.
I was so nervous.
I was surprised by the characters.
I heard their voices.
I was overwhelmed.
The tickets for this tour
will be available from today.
There are two performances.
I can meet many people.
I can meet Sanyuu characters.
I can meet my friends.
I didn't expect to meet you.
You are always with us.
I was so nervous.
I'm so happy.
Thank you.
I want to make this a memory.
We are excited.
We are so excited.
What kind of costumes will you wear?
I don't know.
I'm so excited.
We will run through Nagoya.
Thank you.
We've been doing our best to do a live
show with a big one-man live show.
This time, we did a live show in one
place of the spring tour.
I'm happy to be on the last day of the
tour.
I thought we were getting bigger.
I felt that the place was big.
The back and the side are wide.
The second floor is also big.
I felt that there were a lot of fans.
But it was close to the distance.
I could see their faces clearly.
I was able to feel the enthusiasm from
the fans.
It was a lot of fun.
We were happy when everyone seemed to
be having fun.
We were getting more and more excited.
The live show was getting more and more
exciting.
It was a lot of fun.
I almost cried today.
We've been doing a lot of nostalgic
songs here.
We've been doing it for two or three
years.
I look back on my memories.
I was so happy to think that the tour
was so hot and everyone was so excited.
I'm glad to have more memories.
Let's make more memories.
I think there were people who saw the
Super Toki Tour for the first time in
2022.
Thank you for all the tickets sold out.
I could see everyone's smiling faces.
I was happy to feel everyone's love
while we were listening to our
impressions.
I was happy to see the people in the
back of the second row.
I could see it.
Thank you.
I'm glad that the tour was so hot.
When everyone was leaving the stage,
they said,
I love you all.
The members were so cute.
I'm glad that we were able to
communicate with each other.
I was able to spend a lot of time.
There were so many people.
When I was sitting down, I could see
everyone's faces clearly.
I was so grateful.
In the middle of summer, we will hold a
JEP tour in July and August.
It's not just JEP.
We will hold a live show with Sanrio
characters in six places.
The PR staff were surprised.
We were surprised when we first heard
it.
I really enjoyed the set tour last
year.
It was fun to go out with everyone for
the first time.
It was also fun to meet the local
people for the first time.
I want to go to Hokkaido again.
I want to go to Sendai.
I want to go to Fukuoka.
I want to go to Aichi.
I want to go to Osaka.
I want to enjoy it.
Thank you for always supporting us.
It was the first live show in two years
since we formed the Super Tokimeki
Channel.
I hope we can continue to deliver a
live show that you can believe in us and
follow us.
Please continue to support us.
Aki-chan said a lot of good things.
We also...
I'm getting wet.
We also have Nagoya.
We have a lot of live shows waiting for
us.
We will do our best to have a lot of
fun with everyone.
Thank you.
Bye bye.
I will not step on the brake at full
speed.
So, please follow me.
I like you, I like you, I like you, I
like you, I like you, I like you, I like
you
The reason I exist is because of you
Spinning girl
I can't stop crying, crying, crying
I'm loving you more than I can bear
Let's go! Jump!
I'm savoring every single drop of it
I want to love you so much, so much, so
much
That it's unbelievable
Ready, set, go!
I want to be with you forever
I'm not afraid
You're in love too, right?
If you like this video, if you think
it's cute, if you want to get a score,
please subscribe to our channel and
click the like button!
Please!
Please leave a comment too!
Please subscribe to our channel!
Why is it that when I smile, the world
seems to shine?
I can turn my umbrella around and feel
better
Because I can't walk without it
I'm sure someone is crying somewhere
I wonder if I'll get wet again
somewhere and not feel cold
I'm sure someone is crying somewhere
I just want to share my feelings
A scenery I don't know yet in front of
my eyes
Look, let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye
Thank you for yesterday
The city after the rain is colored
On the canvas of my damaged heart
I'll draw a fragment of the future
It will guide me
Now I can say
The reason for my tears
When I'm lost, I remember right away
Even if it rains, I'll smile
Look, let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye
Thank you for yesterday
The city after the rain is glittering
My heart is like a sunny day
I'll ring the bell of the rainbow
I'll play the rainbow piano
Goodbye, goodbye
Thank you for yesterday
The city after the rain is glittering
My heart is like a flower
I'll dry my tears
I'll wear a rainbow dress
La la la la la la la